

EDUCATION

(2019-2023)

Bachelor in Software Engineering / NUML Islamabad CGPA 3.4

(2017-2019)

FSC with Pre-Engineering / IMCG F-7/4 Margalla, Islamabad Grade: A

(2015-2017)

Matric with Science / IMSG F-7/2, Islamabad Grade: A+

(2023)

NGIRI Ignite Wining for Final Year Project (FYP) / NUML, Islamabad

• (2023)

Web Scrapping / Online sources

KEY SKILLS

- ✓ Front-end Web UI framework and tools.
- ✓ Git (push pull requests, commits).



✓ JavaScript, Material UI, Bootstrap.



✓ React JS, React Native.



✓ REST API, Express, Node, PHP,MongoDB.



Multi-Tasking, Problem Solving.





Samreen Karim

Full Stack Developer

ABOUT ME

I am a recent graduate with a Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering, having 1 year of experience in designing and building Web and Mobile Applications. I have completed my Final Year Project that aims to address the problem of parking through a React Native application, using Express, Node JS on server side, MongoDB as backend database and Figma for an application design and UI. With my hands-on experience in both front-end and back-end development, I am well-equipped to contribute to an organization's growth and success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2023 - Present.

Full Stack Developer (On-site) - Codrivity

- ✓ Utilizing my expertise in web development, working in React JS, Shopify and API Integration from Django backend.
- ✓ I continue to expand my skill set by learning web scraping techniques.
- ✓ I learned to work within deadlines and enhance my leadership skills.

December 2022 – February 2023.

Front & Backend Developer Intern (Remote) - BOT Solutions

- ✓ "E-Installment Application" Responsive application in PHP with MySQL as a backend database.
- ✓ "Customer-Developer Relation" MERN stack application using MongoDB as the backend database and Express on the server.
- ✓ I learned to work in different frameworks, which allowed me to work in a team as well as helped me develop time management skills.

November 2022 – December 2022

Coffee Shop MERN Application

- ✓ Developed a responsive MERN stack application for coffee selling as a semester project.
- ✓ I learned to design responsive website using ReactJS, Express, and NodeJS.

September 2022 – October 2022

Flower Selling Responsive Website

- ✓ Developed a responsive website for flower selling shop as my semester project using pure HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP
- ✓ I learned to design responsive website using HTML, CSS, JS, and PHP in a single website.